BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6725: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1964-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/17/1964 and expires on 7/31/1965. Covers 6500 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1965 and expires on 8/3/1968. Covers 6500 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 5: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 8/4/1968 and expires on 8/7/1971. Covers 6000 workers in New Jersey
  - Code no.6726: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1960-1973 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1960-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 7/23/1960 and expires on 1/25/1964. Covers 1700 workers in Maryland; Delaware
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1960-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 1/26/1964 and expires on 1/21/1967. Covers 2125 workers in Maryland; Delaware
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1967-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 1/22/1967 and expires on 7/19/1969. Covers 2300 workers in Maryland; Delaware
    - Item 5: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1969-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 7/20/1969 and expires on 7/17/1971. Covers 2300 workers in Maryland; Delaware
    - Item 6: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1971-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 7/18/1971 and expires on 8/26/1972. Covers 3000 workers in Maryland; Delaware
    - Item 7: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 8/27/1972 and expires on 8/25/1973. Covers 4237 workers in Maryland; Delaware
  - Code no.6729: Food Store Operators in Alameda County, California and Retail Clerks International Association Local 870, 1953- 1970 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Food Store Operators in Alameda County, California and Retail Clerks International Association Local 870, 1953-1960; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1953 and expires on 9/1/1960. Covers 4500 workers in Alameda, CA
    - Item 2: Food Store Operators in Alameda County, California and Retail Clerks International Association Local 870, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1964 and expires on 3/1/1967. Covers 4150 workers in Alameda, CA
    - Item 3: Food Store Operators in Alameda County, California and Retail Clerks International Association Local 870, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1968 and expires on 12/31/1970. Covers 4150 workers in Alameda, CA
  - Code no.6730: Food Employers, Inc. and Food and Drug Clerks Union Local 1092, 1960-1969 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Food Employers, Inc. and Food and Drug Clerks Union Local 1092, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1960 and expires on 5/1/1962. Covers 1800 workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 2: Food Employers, Inc. and Food and Drug Clerks Union Local 1092, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 4/29/1962 and expires on 4/2/1964. Covers 1800 workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 3: Food Employers, Inc. and Food and Drug Clerks Union Local 1092, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 5/3/1964 and expires on 4/29/1967. Covers 2500 workers in Portland, OR
    - Item 4: Food Employers, Inc. and Food and Drug Clerks Union Local 1092, 1967-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 4/30/1967 and expires on 5/3/1969. Covers 2500 workers in Portland, OR
  - Code no.6732: St. Louis Chain Stores and Supermarkets and Amalgamated Butchers and Meat Cutters Local 88, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: St. Louis Chain Stores and Supermarkets and Amalgamated Butchers and Meat Cutters Local 88, 1959-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1959 and expires on 1/26/1963. Covers 2500 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: St. Louis Chain Stores and Supermarkets and Amalgamated Butchers and Meat Cutters Local 88, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 1/27/1963 and expires on 1/30/1965. Covers 2100 workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Code no.6734: Kosher Meat Markets of New York, New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 234, 1959- 1968 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Kosher Meat Markets of New York, New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 234, 1959-1960; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 3/6/1959 and expires on 12/17/1960. Covers 1800 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: Kosher Meat Markets of New York, New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 234, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1960 and expires on 12/15/1962. Covers 1800 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: Kosher Meat Markets of New York, New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 234, 1963-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 11/26/1963 and expires on 12/19/1964. Covers 1600 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 4: Kosher Meat Markets of New York, New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 234, 1965-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1965 and expires on 12/12/1966. Covers 1500 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 5: Kosher Meat Markets of New York, New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 234, 1967-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 2/17/1967 and expires on 12/14/1968. Covers 1500 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.6735: Food Stores in Minneapolis, Minnesota and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 653, 1959- 1968 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Food Stores in Minneapolis, Minnesota and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 653, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1959 and expires on 3/1/1962. Covers 5500 workers in Minneapolis, MN
    - Item 2: Food Stores in Minneapolis, Minnesota and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 653, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1962 and expires on 3/1/1965. Covers 5500 workers in Minneapolis, MN
    - Item 3: Food Stores in Minneapolis, Minnesota and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 653, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1965 and expires on 3/1/1968. Covers 5500 workers in Minneapolis, MN
  - Code no.6736: Sacramento Valley Employers' Council and Retail Clerks Union Local 588, 1961-1971 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Sacramento Valley Employers' Council and Retail Clerks Union Local 588, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 22)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1961 and expires on 4/30/1964. Covers 2800 workers in Sacramento, CA; Yolo, CA; Placer, CA; El Dorado, CA; Amador, CA; Calaveras, CA; Tuolomne, CA; Stainslaus, CA
    - Item 2: Sacramento Valley Employers' Council and Retail Clerks Union Local 588, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 22)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1964 and expires on 4/30/1967. Covers 3500 workers in Sacramento, CA; Yolo, CA; Placer, CA; El Dorado, CA; Amador, CA; Calaveras, CA; Tuolomne, CA; Stainslaus, CA
    - Item 3: Sacramento Valley Employers' Council and Retail Clerks Union Local 588, 1967-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 22)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1967 and expires on 4/30/1968. Covers 3500 workers in Sacramento, CA; Yolo, CA; Placer, CA; El Dorado, CA; Amador, CA; Calaveras, CA; Tuolomne, CA; Stainslaus, CA
    - Item 4: Sacramento Valley Employers' Council and Retail Clerks Union Local 588, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 22)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1968 and expires on 5/31/1971. Covers 2800 workers in Sacramento, CA; Yolo, CA; Placer, CA; El Dorado, CA; Amador, CA; Calaveras, CA; Tuolomne, CA; Stainslaus, CA
  - Code no.6737: Kansas City Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 576, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Kansas City Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 576, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 10/8/1961 and expires on 10/6/1963. Covers 1100 workers in Kansas City, KS
    - Item 2: Kansas City Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 576, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 11/20/1961 and expires on 10/6/1963. Covers 1100 workers in Kansas City, KS
    - Item 3: Kansas City Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 576, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 10/7/1963 and expires on 10/3/1965. Covers 1150 workers in Kansas City, KS
    - Item 4: Kansas City Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 576, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 12/26/1963 and expires on 10/3/1965. Covers 1150 workers in Kansas City, KS
  - Code no.6742: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. Milwaukee and Retail Store Employees Union Local 444, 1959-1964 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. Milwaukee and Retail Store Employees Union Local 444, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 24)
      Agreement effective 10/22/1959 and expires on 10/21/1961. Covers 3500 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. Milwaukee and Retail Store Employees Union Local 444, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 24)
      Agreement effective 10/22/1961 and expires on 10/24/1964. Covers 2500 workers in Milwaukee, WI
  - Code no.6743: Retail Meat Dealers Associations, Chain Store Operators and Independent Retail Meat Markets and Butcher's Union Local 115, 1959-1964 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Dealers Associations, Chain Store Operators and Independent Retail Meat Markets and Butcher's Union Local 115, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 25)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1959 and expires on 10/1/1961. Covers 1170 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Dealers Associations, Chain Store Operators and Independent Retail Meat Markets and Butcher's Union Local 115, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 25)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1959 and expires on 10/1/1961. Covers 1190 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 3: Retail Meat Dealers Associations, Chain Store Operators and Independent Retail Meat Markets and Butcher's Union Local 115, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 25)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1961 and expires on 10/1/1964. Covers 1675 workers in San Francisco, CA
  - Code no.6744: Retail Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Local Union 1288, 1961-1971 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Retail Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Local Union 1288, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 4/2/1961 and expires on 3/31/1964. Covers 1600 workers in Merced, CA; Mariposa, CA; Madera, CA; Fresno, CA; Tulare, CA; King, CA
    - Item 3: Retail Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Local Union 1288, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 4/2/1964 and expires on 3/31/1967. Covers 1600 workers in Merced, CA; Mariposa, CA; Madera, CA; Fresno, CA; Tulare, CA; King, CA
    - Item 4: Retail Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Local Union 1288, 1967-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1967 and expires on 4/1/1968. Covers 2000 workers in Merced, CA; Mariposa, CA; Madera, CA; Fresno, CA; Tulare, CA; King, CA
    - Item 5: Retail Food and Liquor Employers and Retail Clerks Local Union 1288, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 26)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1968 and expires on 5/31/1971. Covers 2000 workers in Merced, CA; Mariposa, CA; Madera, CA; Fresno, CA; Tulare, CA; King, CA
  - Code no.6745: Jewel Tea Company, Inc. and United Retail Workers Union, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Jewel Tea Company, Inc. and United Retail Workers Union, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 12/6/1959 and expires on 12/30/1961. Covers 5900 workers in Lake, IN; Cook, IL; DuPage, IL; Lake, IL; Kane, IL; McHenry, IL; Will, IL
    - Item 2: Jewel Tea Company, Inc. and United Retail Workers Union, 1961-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 27)
      Agreement effective 12/31/1961 and expires on 1/2/1965. Covers 6000 workers in Lake, IN; Cook, IL; DuPage, IL; Lake, IL; Kane, IL; McHenry, IL; Will, IL
  - Code no.6747: Kroger Co. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Kroger Co. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 9/10/1961 and expires on 9/14/1963. Covers 1200 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 2: Kroger Co. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 28)
      Agreement effective 9/15/1963 and expires on 9/18/1965. Covers 1500 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
  - Code no.6748: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Locals 1059, 31, 1552, 1961-1974 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Locals 1059, 31, 1552, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 10/29/1961 and expires on 10/26/1963. Covers 1000 workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 2: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Locals 1059, 31, 1552, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 10/27/1963 and expires on 10/29/1966. Covers 1000 workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 3: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Locals 1059, 31, 1552, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 10/30/1966 and expires on 11/1/1969. Covers 1000 workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 4: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Locals 1059, 31, 1552, 1969-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 11/2/1969 and expires on 11/6/1971. Covers 1200 workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 5: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Locals 1059, 31, 1552, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 29)
      Agreement effective 11/7/1971 and expires on 11/9/1974. Covers 1600 workers in Columbus, OH
  - Code no.6749: Wyatt Food Stores and Retail Clerks Union Locals 368, 1549, 1960-1966 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Wyatt Food Stores and Retail Clerks Union Locals 368, 1549, 1960-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 30)
      Agreement effective 8/14/1960 and expires on 8/10/1963. Covers 750 workers in Dallas, TX; Fort Worth, TX
    - Item 2: Wyatt Food Stores and Retail Clerks Union Locals 368, 1549, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 30)
      Agreement effective 8/11/1963 and expires on 8/13/1966. Covers 750 workers in Dallas, TX; Fort Worth, TX
  - Code no.6751: Loblaw, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen Local 1, 1961-1974 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Loblaw, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen Local 1, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 4/27/1961 and expires on 5/5/1963. Covers 1800 workers in Utica, NY
    - Item 2: Loblaw, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen Local 1, 1965-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 6/6/1965 and expires on 6/4/1967. Covers 1800 workers in Utica, NY
    - Item 3: Loblaw, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen Local 1, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 6/4/1967 and expires on 6/7/1970. Covers 1900 workers in Utica, NY
    - Item 4: Loblaw, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen Local 1, 1970-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 6/7/1970 and expires on 6/10/1973. Covers 1900 workers in Utica, NY
    - Item 5: Loblaw, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen Local 1, 1973-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Agreement effective 6/10/1973 and expires on 6/9/1974. Covers 2000 workers in Utica, NY
  - Code no.6752: Penn Fruit Store Operation and IBT Local 929, 1959-1970 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Penn Fruit Store Operation and IBT Local 929, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 8/2/1959 and expires on 4/1/1962. Covers 2100 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 2: Penn Fruit Store Operation and IBT Local 929, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 4/2/1962 and expires on 7/5/1964. Covers 2100 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 3: Penn Fruit Store Operation and IBT Local 929, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 7/6/1964 and expires on 7/5/1967. Covers 2150 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 4: Penn Fruit Store Operation and IBT Local 929, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 32)
      Agreement effective 7/6/1967 and expires on 1/10/1970. Covers 3000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Code no.6753: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1393, 1959-1970 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1393, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 8/8/1959 and expires on 6/2/1962. Covers 5000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 2: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1394, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 6/3/1962 and expires on 3/6/1965. Covers 5500 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 3: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1395, 1965-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 3/7/1965 and expires on 7/8/1967. Covers 5485 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 4: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council Locals 1349, 1357, 1358, 1360, 1361, 1371, 1396, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 33)
      Agreement effective 7/9/1967 and expires on 1/10/1970. Covers 6100 workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Code no.6755: Retail Grocers Association and Retail Store Employees Union Local 428, 1959-1968 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Retail Grocers Association and Retail Store Employees Union Local 428, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1959 and expires on 3/31/1961. Covers 2500 workers in Santa Clara, CA; East Palo Alto, CA; North Palo Alto, CA; Menlo Park, CA
    - Item 2: Retail Grocers Association and Retail Store Employees Union Local 428, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1961 and expires on 3/31/1964. Covers 1800 workers in Santa Clara, CA; East Palo Alto, CA; North Palo Alto, CA; Menlo Park, CA
    - Item 3: Retail Grocers Association and Retail Store Employees Union Local 428, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1964 and expires on 3/31/1967. Covers 2500 workers in Santa Clara, CA; East Palo Alto, CA; North Palo Alto, CA; Menlo Park, CA
    - Item 4: Retail Grocers Association and Retail Store Employees Union Local 428, 1967-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 34)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1967 and expires on 3/31/1968. Covers 3381 workers in Santa Clara, CA; East Palo Alto, CA; North Palo Alto, CA; Menlo Park, CA
  - Code no.6756: West Bay Association of Food Industries, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 648, 1961-1970 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: West Bay Association of Food Industries, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 648, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1961 and expires on 12/31/1963. Covers 2250 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 2: West Bay Association of Food Industries, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 648, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1964 and expires on 12/31/1966. Covers 2000 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 3: West Bay Association of Food Industries, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 648, 1967-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1967 and expires on 12/31/1967. Covers 2800 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 4: West Bay Association of Food Industries, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 648, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 35)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1968 and expires on 12/31/1970. Covers 2800 workers in San Francisco, CA
  - Code no.6758: Safeway Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 400, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 36)